ADRIAN SZONYI

Head of Account Management APAC

ABOUT ME

I'm passionate about content creation in all forms and have video experience. I love working with NFP clients and businesses that are focused on delivering for a purpose. I am also currently studying to become a frontend developer. I'm a keen tennis player, love movies and shooting/editing my own content. Here is a link to my portfolio site:

https://adrian-szonyi.github.io/AdrianSzonyiPortfolio/ Here is my Github Profile: https://github.com/Adrian-szonyi

EDUCATION

2021 - Present • University of Sydney: Full Stack Development part-time course

2011 - 2015 • University of Sydney: Bachelor of Economics with Honours in Business Information Systems

EXPERIENCE

2021 - present Shootsta

Shootsta is a video production/Tech start up that trains businesses to make their own video content which is then edited by Shootsta in 24/48 hours. I manage a team of 7 Account Managers with a portfolio of 225 accounts across APAC totalling over \$9M in Annual Recurring Revenue (ARR). Shootsta helps upskill businesses to make content for their YouTube channels.

Head of Account Management APAC:

- While managing my own portfolio of 25 accounts I was also managing the teams performance to hit quarterly growth targets of 20%
- I reduced the client churn rate by 50% in 12 months compared with previous calendar year renewal rate totalling \$1.5M in saved ARR
- Worked closely with many NFP organisations across Australia on content strategy, marketing campaigns and increasing fundraising results through video

2019 - 2021 Shootsta

Head of Account Management AUS

- Managed a team of 6 Account Managers; Team KPIs included: 90% retention, 20% quarterly revenue growth, 4 client testimonials a quarter and cross selling new products and subscription adoption
- Consulted on the content strategy for CPA with their digital marketing team to improve sign ups for their new campaigns
- Created and ran a workshop for NZ clients on tips for filming with their phones
- Achieved 90% portfolio retention for client renewals

ADRIAN SZONYI

Head of Account Management APAC

2015-2019 OniGroup

OniGroup was named Google Cloud Partner of the year in 2018. They are a reseller of Google Enterprise technologies. For the 4 years that I worked at OniGroup I sold to clients every Google Enterprise solution (except for Adwords). While working as a Cloud Consultant I sold and delivered digital transformation services for G Suite and data analytics. I also worked on Cloud IoT solutions, Google Analytics and designed dashboards for clients using DataStudio.

Cloud Consultant

- Managed partnership relationship with Google Cloud representatives
- Managed a portfolio of 40 Google Maps, Google Analytics, G Suite and cloud services accounts for renewals and growth
- Ran change management and digital transformation workshops for clients transitioning from Microsoft to G Suite
- Achieved 25% YoY portfolio growth

SKILLS

Video Production	HTML + CSS
Partnerships	Javascript
Sales	Management
Negotiations	Git
Project Management	JQuery
Tennis	Node.JS

PROJECTS

FunNightIn: Randomly pick your next meal and a movie to watch: https://adrian-szonyi.github.io/FunNightIn/PlanIt: Event planning application, book your next party, choose from our list of approved vendors https://planit-events.herokuapp.com/